genealogyintime.com 2009-08-05

# Privacy Policy - GenealogyInTime.com

##   Privacy Policy

Last Revised: 29 March 2009

We value your privacy and we are committed to safeguarding it.

Any personally identifiable information that you provide to us (such as your email address, name or street address) will be treated as strictly confidential.

Our web site uses ‘cookies’ to improve the quality of our service. We track user trends and the general flow of internet traffic on our web site. As well, we use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our web site. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, click [here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/). You may specifically op out of Google ad cookies (including interest-based advertising) by clicking [here](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).

If you subscribe to our broadcast email service, we will collect and store your e-mail address. We will not sell, rent or share your email address with anyone. You may unsubscribe from our email service at any time by clicking on the unsubscribe link included in every broadcast email. 

If you send us an email (or other form of communication) we will store your communication to help us process your request or inquiry. We will not add you email address to our broadcast email service without your permission.

This privacy policy applies only to our web site GenealogyInTime.com and our broadcast email service. We do not exercise privacy control over other web sites. 

MissingLink Software Corporation is an independent software company located in Ottawa, Canada and is governed by the laws of the province of Ontario, Canada. All our employees have been trained in the proper care and handling of personally identifiable information.

If you have any questions, comments or concerns about our privacy policy then please drop us a line at [letusknow@GenealogyInTime.com](mailto:letusknow@GenealogyInTime.com)
